到目前为止的闪耀色彩
Maybe, someday, you'll be able to meet thefeelings you have within yourself, too.
マノちゃんの気持ちにも いつか出会えるんじゃないのかな
And perhaps the feelings you have,are already starting to grow inside of you.
それに 本当はもう 自分の中に生まれているのかも
Inside of me, there's already...
わたしの中にはもう
Surely...
きっと
Tomorrow's concert...
明日のステージ
I want to do my best together with everyone!
みんなと一緒に 頑張りたい
The show starts in 10 minutes! Please make your way inside quickly!
開演10分前です お早めにお入りください
I'm so nervous!
ドキドキするね
Wow! Look, look!
わ 見て見て
howa
Everyone's waiting for us!
みんな  待ってるんだ
Yeah!
うん
Whoa...This is intense.
うわ やばっ
Don't worry. The effort we've put in won't let us down.
大丈夫 積み重ねてきたものは裏切らないさ
Yeah, I think you're right!
うん そんな気してきた
Ma-no!
ナホ
howa
The audience?
お客さん
Yeah... um, you see, well...
うん あのね えっと
It feels different than usual.
いつもより
All right, looks like everyone's here!
さあ みんな揃ったな
howa
Let's get going!
行こうか
不知道说了什么
We'll deliver it perfectly!
バッチリ届けるぽい!
Deliver what exactly?
うん 何をっすか
补语气词
I guess you could say, to all our hard work.
積み重ね かな
I'm so excited!
わくわくします
Yeah, let's have lots of fun!
うん いっぱい楽しもう
I wonder if everyone will be surprised!
みんなびっくりしてくれるかな
Yeah, I'm sure... they'll be surprised and happy!
うん きっと びっくりして ハッピーに
It's exciting, isn't it?
ワクワクするね
うん
All right, Mano! Do the thing!
じゃあ まの あれ
Let's make this a super fun event... For everyone who came here today!
今日 ここに来てくれた皆さんのために いっぱい 楽しいイベントにしましょう
283 Pro Trick or—
283プロ
トリック—
Happy! Yeah!
オアハッピー 补
This is seat A-6.
A6のお席です
Tonight is... Halloween.
今宵は ハロウィン
The time for it to begin...
始まりの時が
...is drawing near.
近づいている
It's that... once-a-year...
それは 年に一度も
...party of evil spirits.
悪霊達の パーティー
うわ
There are so many ghosts!
お化けが いっぱいです
Oh no!
大変
What do we do?!
どうすんだ
There's only one way to chase away these ghosts!
このお化けを追いはらう方法は ただ一つ
And that's by giving them a real fright!
それは びっくりさせちゃうこと
10 seconds left.
10秒前
So tonight, it's up to us!
だから 今夜はわたしたちで
To give them a scare!
びっくりさせて
5 seconds left.
5秒前
Let's come together as one!
一つになって
3!
2!
1!
Let's all get happy together!
みんなで ハッピーになっちゃおう
Illumination Stars!
イルミネーションスターズ
Everyone! Welcome to 283 PRODUCTIONS' Halloween Party - Happy Surprise Trick!
みなさん 283プロハロウィーンパーティーハッピーサプライズトリックへ
Welcome!
ようこそ
L'Antica!
アンティータ
Today is a special, once-a-year party! We hope you have a great time!
今日は年に一度の スペシャルなパーティーばい 楽しんでいってね
Houkago Climax Girls!
放課後クライマックスガールズ
It's an incredibly fun party packed with lots and lots of surprises!
びっくりがたくさんつまった とっても楽しいパーティーです
Straylight!
Straylight
Are you all ready to have fun?!
楽しむ準備 できてるっすか
Alstroemeria!
アデストロメリア
Everyone! Let's have fun together until the very end!
みんな 最後まで一緒に 楽しもうね
Now then, let's get right to it...!
それでは 早速こちらを
Please take a look!
ご覧ください
All shuffle!
オールシャッフル
Tonight, we'll be shuffling the members and bringing you special performances!
今夜はなんと メンバーをシャッフルしてパフォーマンスをお届けします
One after another, they'll appear! What kind of combinations will we see?
どんどん登場 どんな組み合わせになるのかな
And the first shuffle team is...
最初のシャッフルチームは
Thank you very much!
红豆泥阿里嘎多
The next shuffle team is...
続いてのシャッフルチームは
Here they are!
こちらです
Even on this night of a light-filled feast...
光あふれる 宴の夜も
This world is full of things unseen...
この世は見えぬ ものばかり
Light within the light...
光の中の 光
Darkness within the darkness...
闇の中の 闇
Within the depths... of the heart...
心の うち
The door is already open.
扉はもう 開いている
We are already here.
私たちはもう ここにいる
You can't see us.
見えない
You don't notice us.
気づかない
No matter where you are...
たとえどこにいようとも
Yes, you all are already...
そう お前たちはもう
Together with us.
私たちと 共にいる
A dazzling feast of darkness...
めくるめく闇の痛み
...You cannot escape.
もう 逃げられない
Thank you guys!
呃呃
All right! It's time for the final stretch!
さあ いよいよラストスパートだよ
The next team is...
次のチームは
Here they are!
こちらです
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございました
And now, the final shuffle team is...?
最後のシャッフルチームは
Can you guess who it is?
誰だかわかるかな
All right! Let's get pumped up!
さあ もりあがっていきますよ
If you don't get excited....!
盛り上がらなきゃ
We'll play a trick on you!
いたずらしちゃうぞ
Everyone! Here we go!
补
3! 2! 1! Boom!
Here I go!
行ってきまーす
Thank you!
ありがとう
Now, let's call everyone over! Everyone!
それではここで みんなを呼んじゃいましょう
Everyone!
みんな~!
Come on over!
おいで~!
Okay, the next one will be our final song!
さて 次が最後の曲になりました
えっ?
What?! A surprise?!
何 サプライズ!?
Huh, what is it, what is it?!
えっ 何が何が
えっ
Is there more?!
まだあるんですか？
We did it! We did it, yay!
やった やったbaibaibaibaibai chinchinchinchinchin
Wow...
や—
they really got us there.
やられちゃったねぇ
Yeah, they sure did!
アッハハ だな
Please continue with the MC!
Today, being able to enjoy Halloween with everyone,
今日は 皆さんと一緒にハロウィンを楽しめて
and sharing such wonderful news at the end, made this an incredibly happy day!
最後には 嬉しいお知らせもできて
すっごく ハッピーな1日でした
Thank you very much!
ありがとうございました
ありがとうございましたありがとうございました
And now, for our final song! Please listen!
それでは最後の曲です 聴いてください
Thank you very much!
补
Bye-bye!
字幕制作：北宇治字幕组Deep State翻译：FFU2后期：Scrpr
Great job, Mano-chan. Were you watching?
マノちゃん お疲れ様
見てたの?
Ah, thank you!
howa お疲れ様です
Um... today, I felt like... I could feel the fans closer than usual.
えっと…今日はなんだか…ファンの皆さんを…いつもより…近くに感じて
I'm sure the audience felt the same way, too.
お客さんも きっとそう思ってる
Great job, everyone!
みんな お疲れ様
Thank you for your hard work!
お疲れ様でした
Yeah, it turned out to be a great event.
いやー いいイベントになったな
It's all thanks to everyone's hard work during the preparations.
準備を頑張ってくれた みんなのおかげだやった
We did it!
Ah! We were surprised, too! That last announcement...!
おちらも驚いたと 最後のやつ
Haha,
アッハハ
did it surprise you?
驚いてくれたか
I wanted to make sure that all of you,
頑張ってるみんなが
who are working so hard, can shine even brighter.
もっと輝けるように な
Also... everyone,
それと みんな
there's something important I need to talk to you about regarding what's coming next.
今後のことで 大事な話があるんだ